I'm Mizuki Kirihara, in charge of Candy Tune Blue.
Myself from my point of view? I'm not sure.
I think I'm serious. I'm cheerful.
But even the people around me say I'm very serious.
Excuse me, Poncatcher... about an episode in high school... when I was in the dance club... we were in the dance club, and during morning practice and club activities, I'd always be the first one to show up.
I was in the dance club, and during morning practice and club activities, I would be the first one to take out all the mirrors, and I would do my own practice by myself in the car. When I was born, I was dancing all the time, even when I watched home videos of my childhood,
There are images of me dancing to music coming from a toy piano, like a kindergarten recital, you know? Playdates.
I was the kind of kid who was always dancing in the middle of the stage.
I don't know what it was.
I've always loved to dance, but I never had a chance.
I've always been a dancer.
I've always been a dancer,
I have a habit of trying to stand out.
I have a habit of trying to stand out,
So, it's fine if I dance alone,
But in an idol group, you have to fit in with the people around you.
Nowadays, there are so many people in a group,
If you don't match them properly, you look disjointed.
Like matching them.
I had a lot of trouble getting the angles of my fingers to match. I still do.
As for gravure, my father likes comic books.
You know, there are thick comic books.
Like Shonendan.
He used to buy those comics and put them on the stairs when he finished reading them. At home.
And I was in the second grade, I think.
At that time, I saw that there was an older sister on the cover.
I saw her and thought she was cute.
That was the first time I was exposed to Gravure,
Then, when I became a high school student, the idols who inspired me to become an idol were the ones who were actively involved in gravure, such as taking movies in swimsuits,
And I always wanted to try it myself,
I've always wanted to try it myself.
I have always wanted to do gravure, and I have always wanted to do it myself,
I think my thinking about gravure will probably change. From now on.
Hmm.
I moved to Tokyo alone when I was a sophomore in high school, so I had no friends over here and no one I could rely on, so I still get very spoiled when I see my family. I feel like I am back to high school.
I don't have this.
I've always had the mindset of living for the sake of others,
I'm trying to do what people are looking for,
I'm not obsessed with myself or anything.
I can't wait to meet you all.
I really love you all, and I can't wait to meet you all.
I'm so happy!
I want to make a group where everyone can be who they want to be and everyone can be happy.
When I think about various options, I think about my future self, my family, and so on,
I want to be in an environment where everyone can be happy,
I wanted to be an idol in an environment where everyone can be happy.
That's why I chose to come here to perform idols from Harajuku, Japan to the world.
I think that I have become stronger than before by using various things from the past as weapons,
I hope to be able to save even more people.
Q. What is Candy Tune like?
Candy Tune is my youth.
Q. Are you in your youth?
Yes, very much! Very much!